National Organization for Women, New York State Chapter; Records apap029
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Lobbyist Files, 1972-2011; 4; 8.0 cubic ft.
  - Education (2 of 2), 1977-1979; 1981-1984 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Education: NOW Bill, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Education Statewide Advisory Council on Equal Opportunity for Women, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Education - Title IX, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Educational Programing at Seneca Falls, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Emancipation of Children, Undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Emergency Contraceptive Research, 1998-200 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Emergency Response Preparedness: Hazardous Material Transportation Accidents, Undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Empire State Wage Act, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Employment, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Employment, 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Employment Bills, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Employment Mailings, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Endorsement Of Political Candidates, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Equal Employment Rights (1 of 2), 1984-1987 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Equal Employment Rights (2 of 2), 1984-1987 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Equal Rights Amendment (1 of 3), 1974-1976; 1979; 1981-1984; Undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Equal Rights Amendment (2 of 3), 1974-1976; 1979; 1981-1984; Undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Equal Rights Amendment (3 of 3), 1974-1976; 1979; 1981-1984; Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Equal Rights Amendment (1 of 4), 1984; Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Equal Rights Amendment (2 of 4), 1984; Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Equal Rights Amendment (3 of 4), 1984; Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Equal Rights Amendment (4 of 4), 1984; Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Equitable Distribution, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - ERA Assembly Debate, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - ERA Drive, 1983; 1988 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - ERA Impact Clearing House (1 of 2), 1981; 1983 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - ERA Impact Clearing House (2 of 2), 1981; 1983 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Estate Powers and Trust Law, Undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Event Updates, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Exclusion of Women from Longshore, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Executive Summary and Proposed Legislation, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Exposing People To HIV/AIDS, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Extension Of DNA Analysis of Rape Kits, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Family Court Act, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Family Court and Domestic Relations Law, 1976-1979 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Family Medical Leave Act, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Family Planning Advocates, 1988-1992; Undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Family Planning Services, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Female Genital Mutilation, 1987; 1997; 2005 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Feminist Sheila Fieger, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Fetal Death, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Fetal Toxicology, 2000; Undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Finance Vice President Mailing, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Forms, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Freedom Of Choice Act, 1989-1992 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Garrison Report, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Gay and Lesbian Mamas, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Gender Balance, 19910-1991 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Gender Balance in the Workplace, 1990; 1994; Undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Glass Ceiling In Gubernatorial Appointments, 1997; 2007 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - "The Good Guys and Gals" Legislative Representatives For Social Concerns, 1978-1981 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Governor's Program Bill, 1990; 1993 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Governor's Veto's, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Gun Ban Effort, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Health, 1982; 1992; 1997-1998; Undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Health and Social Services, 1975-1978 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Healthcare and Contraception, 2000-2002 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Healthcare Proxy, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Hearing, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Higher Education, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - HIV/AIDS Bills, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - HMO, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Human Rights, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Immigrant Healthcare, 2001; Undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Impaired Newborn Bill, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Important Features Of Lobbying Law, Undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Important Votes, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Imposed Joint Custody, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Incest, 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Incoming Correspondence, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Indecent Material, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Infant Formula, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Internal Procedures, 1985; 1987; 1993; Undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Joint Custody, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Joint Custody Fact Sheet, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Joint Custody - Hatfield and Hyde, 1982; Undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Kathleen Peratis- Testimony, Undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Key Legislative Issue Before 1990 New York State Legislature (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Labor, Health, Higher Education and Social Services, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Late Term Abortion, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Legal Services, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Legislation, 1985-1988; Undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Legislation (1 of 2), 1993-1994; Undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Legislation (2 of 2), 1993-1994; Undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Legislation, 1995; Undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Legislative Agenda, 1984-1988 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Legislative Bill Drafting Commission, Undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Legislative Briefs, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Legislative Budget and Legislative Priorities, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Legislative Correspondence - Sharon Fawley, 1933 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Legislative Issues, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Legislative Memos, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Legislative Memos, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Legislative Memos Sent to Senate or Assembly, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Legislative News Letter, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Legislative Priorities, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Legislative Priorities, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Legislative Priorities, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Legislative Priorities, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Legislative Priorities, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Legislative Priorities, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Legislative Priorities, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Legislative Priorities, 1999-2001 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Legislative Priorities, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Legislative Priorities- Pamphlets, 1988; 1993 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Legislative Program, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Legislative Program, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Legislative Programs, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Recommendations, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Legislative Report Memos, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Legislative Report Memos, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Legislative Reports, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Legislative Reports, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Legislative Reports, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Legislative Reports, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Legislative Reports, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Legislative Survey, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Legislative Updates, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Legislative Updates, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Legislative Updates, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Legislative Updates, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Legislative Updates, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Legislative Updates, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Legislative Updates, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Legislative Updates, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Legislative Updates, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Legislators and Chapters, 1977; Undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Lesbian Rights (1 of 2), 1981; 1999 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Lesbian Rights (2 of 2), 1981; 1999 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Life Insurance, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Lobby Commission, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Lobby Day - March 13, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Lobby Day - March 24, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Lobby Day - March 23, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Lobby Day, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Lobby Support Groups, Undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Lobbying, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Lobbying Act, Undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Lobbyist Column, Undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Lobbyist Introductory Letter, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Lobbyist Reports 1981 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Lobbyist Reports for 1985, Undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Lobbyist Reports for 1986 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Lobbyist Reports for 1988, 1988-1989; Undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Lobbyist Reports for 1990, 1990-1991; Undated (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Lobbyist Reports for 1991, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Lobbyist Reports for 1992 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Lobbyist Reports for 1993, 1993-1994; Undated (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Lobbyist Reports for 1994, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Lobbyist Reports for 1995, 1994-1996 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Lobbyist Reports for 1996, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Lobbyist Reports for 1998, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Lobbyist Reports for 1999, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Lobbyist Reports for 2000 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Lobbyist Reports for 2001, 2000-2001; Undated (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Lobbyist Reports for 2002, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Lobbyist Reports for 2003, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Lobbyist Reports for 2004 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Lobbyist Statement of Registration, 1988-1989; 1993; Undated (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Lobbyist Update to State Legislature, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Longshore Workers, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Mandatory HIV Partner Notification, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Mandatory HIV Testing, 1994-1996; 2007 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Mandatory Medications of Child Custody and Child Support Disputes, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Mandatory Reporting, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Marriage, 1976-1979; 1982 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Marriage and Divorce (1 of 2), 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Marriage and Divorce (2 of 2), 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Maternity Care, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Maternity Care Coverage, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Medicaid, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Medicaid Funding for Abortion, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Meditation and Arbitration, 1985-1998; Undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda, 1975; 1979 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Memos Being Held, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Menacing in the First Degree, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Minors, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Model Support Act, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Municipal Services, 1976-1978 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - National Advocates for Pregnant Women, Undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Need For ERA, 1982; 1984; Undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - No-Fault Divorce, 1981; Undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - No-Fault Divorce - Correspondence, 1990; 1997; 2005-2007 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Notice of Public Hearings - Senate Standing Committee On Children Families, Undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - NOW-NYS Budget, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - NOW-NYS Convention, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - NOW-NYS Legislative Watch, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - NYCLU Timeline of Appropriations Bills in Congress, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - NYS Assembly Task Force On Women's Issues, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - NYS Budget, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - NYS Client Annual Report, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - NYS Commission On Child Support, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - NYS Court Structure, Judicial Reform and Access to Justice, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - NYS Legislative Session Calendar, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - NYS Legislative Session Calendar, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - NYS Legislative Session Calendar, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - NYS Senate Hearing Equal Rights Amendment to the NYS Constitution, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - NYS Senate Voting Record, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - NYS Senate Voting Record on Eliminating State Medicaid Funding For Abortion Services, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - NYS Temporary State Commission on Lobbying, Undated (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Obstetrical Care, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Open Meetings Law/ FOIL, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Outgoing Correspondence, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Paid Family and Medical Leave Act, 1992; 2001; Undated (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Parental Notification, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Partial Birth Abortions, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Patient Information, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Pay Equality, 1984-1988; Undated (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Penal and Civil Rights Law, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Pension Rights, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Pensions, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Personal Property Law, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Pesticide/ Breast Cancer Legislation, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Pesticide Reportings, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Political Organization Finances and Student Fees, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Poverty Bills, 1999; 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Pregnancy Leave, Undated (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Pregnancy Police, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Pregnancy Police, 1997-1999 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Procedural Guidelines For the Interaction of Paid Lobbyists with the Leadership of NOW-NYS, Undated (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Pro-Choice Candidates Recommended for Support by Various Organizations and Individuals, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Proposed Legislative Procedure, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Protective Parent Reform Act, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Public Assistance, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Public Hearing on Newborn Screening, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Questions, Undated (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Rape, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Rape Prevention and Control Program, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Rape and Sexual Assault, 1989-1992 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Rape Treatment, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Ratification of CEDAW, Undated (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Reauthorizing the Violence Against Women Act, 1997-1998; 2000; Undated (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Recognition of Domestic Partners, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Reforming Education for Students with Disabilities, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Reforming Health Care System, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Report of the Subcommittee on Newborn HIV Screening of the NYS AIDS Advisory Council, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Reproductive Bills, 1990; 1999-2002 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Reproductive Rights, 1979-1981; Undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Reproductive Rights, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Reproductive Rights - Bills, 1991; 2001; Undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Resolution in Regard to Welfare Reform Bill, Undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - RU486- French Pill, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Samuel S. Stratton- 28th Distinct, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Senate Committee Agenda and Calendar, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Senate Hearing, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Senate Majority Task Force on Health and Wellness, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Senator Frank Pavadon, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Senator Howard C. Noland - 42nd District, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Sex Discrimination, 1977; 1981-1982; Undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Sex Offenses, 1982; Undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Sexual Abuse, 1982; Undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Sexual Assault Forensic Exam, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Sexual Harassment, Undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Sexual Orientation Non-Discrimination Act (SONDA), 2001-2002; Undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Social Services Law, 1988; Undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Sojourner Truth, 1982; Undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Special Sessions, 1980; Undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Sports, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Stalking and Harassment, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - State Boards and Commissions, Undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - State-by-State Guide to the Welfare Laws Hidden Reproductive Rights Agenda, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - State Fiscal Crisis, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - State Legislative Strategy Conference, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Strip Searchers, 1982; Undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Subscription Agreement, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Surrogacy, 1986-1988 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Surrogacy, 1986-1988; Undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Susan Russell, 1981; Undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Sweatshops, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Task Forces - Mailings, 1982; Undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Teacher Retirement, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Teachers- Plain View - Old Bethpage, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Teen Pregnancy, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Temporary Work Release, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Title X, 1997; Undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Unemployment Insurance, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Unborn Victims of Violence/ Motherhood Protection Act, 1996; 2001-2002; Undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Viagra, Undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Violence Against Women Bills, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Violation of Custody, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Visitation vs Parenting, 1997; Undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Votes of the 101st Congress, Undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Voting Record- NYS Assembly, 1980; Undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Voting Records, 1972; 1981-1982; 1984; Undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Weekly Contact Reports, 1985; Undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - White House- Updates For Women, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Women's Health and Wellness Bills, 2001; Undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Women's Health Care, 1988-1990; Undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Women's "Right to Know" Act, 2001; Undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Women's Study Group, Undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Work and Poverty, 1997-1998; Undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Workers Compensation Survivors, 1982; Undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Mailing Lists, 1974-2005; 5; 3.1 cubic ft.
  Arranged in chronological order.
  This series contains computer printouts and other mailing lists of NOW-NYS and individual chapters.
  Per the memorandum of agreement with NOW-NYS, the membership lists are closed for 50 years from the date of their creation. Therefore, the files in this series will be open to researchers after 50 years.
- NOW Publications, 1971-2009; 6; 5.01 cubic ft.
  This series contains newsletters from various chapters of NOW-NYS as well as newsletters from other chapters across the country. The newsletters provide an insight on the events that local chapters hosted including fundraisers, book readings, marches, and meetings.
  The series also contains a smaller number of NOW-NYS and national NOW publications.
  - Albany Area -NOW, 1975-1977; 1981; 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Albany Area -NOW, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Albany Area -NOW, 1989-1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Albany Area -NOW, 1994-1997; 2002; 2005-2006; Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bay Ridge -NOW, 1981-1983; 1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Bronx -NOW, 1977-1978; 1981-1982; 1984-1985; 1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bronx -NOW, 1988-1991; 1993 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Brooklyn -NOW, 1977-2002 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Brooklyn-Queens -NOW, 2003-2007 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Broome County -NOW, 1985-1989; Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Buffalo and Erie Canal -NOW, 1989; 1993; 1995; 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Buffalo -NOW, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Central NY-NOW, 1975; 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Central NY-NOW, 1985-1988 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Central NY-NOW, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Central NY-NOW, 1991-1992; 2001-2004 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Central Westchester -NOW, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Delaware-Otsego Chapter-NOW, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Do It NOW, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Dunkirk - Fredonia -NOW, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - East End -NOW, 1978; 1986-1993; 2004; Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Erie Canal -NOW, 1973-1974; 1977 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Farmington Valley -NOW, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Finger Lakes -NOW, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Finger Lakes -NOW, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Fulton-Montgomery -NOW, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Genesee Valley -NOW, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Greater Rochester -NOW, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Greater Rochester -NOW, 1988-1991 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Greater Syracuse Chapter -NOW, 1977-1978; 1987 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Greater Syracuse Chapter -NOW, 1981; 1989-1993 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Greenwich -NOW, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Huntington -NOW, 1976; 1984-1985; Undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Huntington -NOW, 1986-1988; 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Long Island -NOW, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Middletown -NOW, Undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Mid-Hudson -NOW, 1974-1976; 1983-1990 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Mid-Hudson -NOW, 1974-1976; 1984-1991 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Mid-Suffolk -NOW, 1978-1984 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Mid-Suffolk -NOW, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Mid-Suffolk -NOW, 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Mid-Suffolk -NOW, 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Mid-Suffolk -NOW, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Mohawk Valley NOW, 1983-1987 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Nassau -NOW, 1976-1978 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Nassau -NOW, 1982-1986 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Nassau -NOW, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Nassau -NOW, 1989-1993 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - National NOW Conference, 1997 (Oversized 6)
  - National NOW Times: The Official Publication of the National Organization for Women, 1981; 1983-1986; 1988-1993 (Oversized 3)
  - National NOW Times: The Official Publication of the National Organization for Women, 1994-2005 (Oversized 4)
  - New City -NOW, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - New York City -NOW, 1986; 1988-1991; 2001; 2005-2006 (Oversized 11)
  - New York City -NOW, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - New York State -NOW, 1971; 1974; 1976-1980 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - NOW -NYS Action Reporter, 1984-1998 (Oversized 2)
  - NOW -NYS Legislative Program, 1979-1984 (Oversized 6)
  - NOW -NYS Reporter, 1998; 2001-2002; 2004-2009 (Oversized 5)
  - Orange County -NOW, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Out-of-State Newsletters -NOW, A-D, 1976-1977; 1980; 1988-1993; Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Includes Arkansas, Arizona, California, Cincinnati (Ohio) Connecticut, Delaware, Dade (County, Florida), District of Columbia.
  - Out-of-State Newsletters -NOW, I-M, 1979-1982; 1989-1992; Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Includes Illinois, Kansas, Kentucky, Louisiana, Maine, Massachusetts, Michigan, Minnesota, Missouri.
  - Out-of-State Newsletters -NOW, N-W, 1973; 1976; 1979-1980; 1989-1991 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Includes Nashville (Tennessee), New Jersey, Ohio, Pennsylvania, Philadelphia (Pennsylvania), Southern Nevada, Texas, Utah, Vermont, Virginia, Washington, West Virginia, Wisconsin.
  - Out-of-State Newsletters -NOW, 1981; 1988-1990; 1992-1993; 1997-1998 (Oversized 12)
    Includes Connecticut, Maryland, Massachusetts, Pennsylvania, Utah, Virginia, and Wichita (Kansas).
  - Putnam -Eastern Dutchess -NOW, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Queens -NOW, 1976; 1978; 1981; 1986 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Rochester -NOW, 1993-1994; 2000 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Rockland County -NOW, 1978; 1990-1991; 1993-1994; Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Saratoga -NOW, 1983; 1991-1993 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - South Nassau -NOW, Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - South Shore -NOW, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - South Suffolk -NOW, 1989; 1991-1992; 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - South Suffolk -NOW, 2005-2008 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Southern Westchester -NOW, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Staten Island -NOW, 1985; 1989; 1990; 1993 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Sullivan-County -NOW, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Tompkins County -NOW, 1985-1988; 1989; 2001; 2006 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Ulster County -NOW, 1985; 1992 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Wayne County -NOW, 1978; 1980 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - West Point -NOW, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Westchester -NOW, 1987-1992; 2000-2006; Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - The Women's Monthly, 1980-1982 (Oversized 6)
- Feminist Publications Collection, 1970-2008; 7; 3.55 cubic ft.